THOMAS MILLER

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER SOLUTIONS ENGINEER

951.532.5663 | tsmiller19@gmail.com | www.thomasmiller.dev | www.linkedin.com/in/thethomasmiller

SUMMARY

I am an empathetic software engineer with nearly a decade of experience working and creating with others. I am passionate about empowering, accessible technology, and am seeking a position where collaboration and growth are valued.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Fellow

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | NEW YORK CITY, NY

MAY 2020- AUG 2020

- Full time fellow in Software Engineering Immersive, building Full Stack Applications with remote teams
- Trained in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Ruby, and Rails
- 4+ Full-Stack Applications including agile development collaboration with GA UX/DI Cohort

Account Manager

PROMPIN' CIRCUMSTANCE | NEW YORK CITY, NY

JUNE 2018 - MAR 2020

- Delivered highest quality technical and customer service to grow prominent client relationships valued at over \$150k annually
- High Profile Clientele, including: Former US Presidents and Vice Presidents, US Congressional Leadership, Robert F. Kennedy Human Rights, The Tonight Show, Watch What Happens: Live!

Operations and Compliance Manager

OPTIONS FOR YOUTH | LOS ANGELES, CA

NOV 2016 - MAY 2018

- Cleaned, prepared, and visualized data to identify and share key trends within the education space.
- Managed State and District Charter School compliance regulations for two charter school sites, two Assistant Principals, Regional Principal, 10+ teachers, and 500+ students.
- Increased failing scores to 96% in less than 2 months by initiating and streamlining site QA procedures and best practices.
- New Employee of the Year June 2017; Received highest rating on annual review, "Among the Best"

Web Designer / Consultant

PATHWAYS TO ADVENTURE | ORANGE, CA

JUNE 2012 - NOV 2016

- Designed, built and managed website, social media, and email services for 501(c)3 non-profit
- Extensive consulting for President and board members on organizational mission, digital presence, and volunteer initiatives

EDUCATION

General Assembly

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE 400+ hours of professional. full-time, full-stack training

University of California San Diego

BA DOUBLE MAJOR: POLITICAL SCIENCE, INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS | THEATRE Magna Cum Laude